"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream Extra Episode"
(Episode 2: First Kiss)
I'm meeting with the
event organizer tonight.
Have dinner on your own.
Man or woman?
None of your business.
I'm your husband. Of
course it's my business.
Does it look good?
Yellowing your hair just
to meet the organizer?
"Yellow" is so tacky. It's blond.
Right.
Blondie.
I wanted nine charity shows,
but the old guy would only offer three.
Old geezer.
I offered to cover the
cost for the other six,
so he could announce
nine shows to the public.
He refused.
He didn't want to lie.
Afraid of the public backlash.
What does any of that have
to do with dyeing your hair?
Nothing.
I want the truth.
I just felt like it.
Does the old guy like blonds?
I don't know about him,
but this young guy does.
I barely walked out the door
and you're already calling.
Are you ever going to let me leave?
Be back before nine.
Got it.
Be good.
I won't be good if you're not around.
All the actors have arrived.
Let's set the audition order in a bit.
Okay.
Hello, Director Lizzy?
Have you arrived yet?
Oh, stuck in traffic?
No problem at all.
Take your time, no rush.
The GPS isn't accurate?
Let me pull up the other map app
and send you the location again.
Okay.
The director can't make it for now.
Hand out the audition
sides to them in a bit.
Will do.
[Summer Epilogue auditions]
Um, excuse me, sir?
Is this the audition for
"Summer's Epilogue"?
Yes. Come on in.
Am I early?
No.
You're right on time.
Why don't you introduce yourself first?
Sure.
Hello, sir. My name is Feng Qinglang.
I'm 21 years old,
studying at Jinling Media College.
My hobbies include hiking
and watching classic movies.
My favorite film is.
"Ye Xiao'e."
Are you familiar with this genre?
Yes, sir.
I've watched several titles.
Are you comfortable doing kiss scenes?
Yes, I can do that.
How far are you willing to go?
Well, I think I'm open to anything.
An actor shouldn't limit himself.
Can you do a kiss scene for us right now?
Absolutely, sir.
Do I have a scene partner?
Yes.
Can I read it with you?
Sure thing, sir.
Which part are we doing?
I've memorized all the lines.
Just kiss me.
Having fun?
I was just trying to stop
you from auditioning.
That way, you wouldn't
meet the young Shi Yuhao.
Excuses.
Why are you back so early?
Didn't you say nine?
If I hadn't come back,
would you have auditioned a bed scene next?
What's wrong, did I ruin your fun?
It was you either way.
The one in the parallel universe wasn't me.
Then you should travel back
to find a younger me, too.
What, go back to change your diapers?
Xu Changyang, you think
I'm getting old, don't you?
You jump at any chance
to chase someone younger.
You're sleeping on the couch tonight.
Are you mad?
I'll throw the tea ball away.
I won't play with it anymore.
I don't have the energy to stay mad at you.
Are you always that
uninhibited when acting?
Kissing a stranger just like that?
I wouldn't have kissed anyone else.
You traveled back in time
just now too, didn't you?
No.
Stubborn as always.
I didn't.
Hey.
Xu Changyang.
I knew you were getting restless.
You just can't help yourself.
Seeing a 21-year-old Feng Qinglang,
you completely lost your head, didn't you?
I gave you a chance
to give me your first kiss.
What's wrong with that?
You actually care about that?
I don't care. I just wanted it.
You wanted it?
If you want it, it's yours.
Now confess.
Where did you come from?
I said, start talking.
Where did you find this body double?
Tricking me into thinking it was time
travel with some high-tech gadget?
You saw the time travel yourself.
I couldn't have faked that.
Seeing isn't always believing.
Come clean.
What is this place...
Shut up.
You don't get a say here.
If you're hiring a double, at least
pick someone who looks like me.
Did my voice really sound that
fake and breathy when I was young?
I wasn't around back then.
How would I know?
Feng Qinglang.
Yeah?
Mm.
(Wilderness lies at the end of the road)